<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        
        <title>
                            Latest Switch Game Metascores on Metacritic
                    </title>
        <link>https://www.metacritic.com</link>
        <description>Keep up on our latest reviews</description>
        
        
                
                
        <language>en-us</language>        
        <copyright>2019 CBS Interactive Inc.</copyright>        
                
                
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>        
                
        <ttl>60</ttl>        
        
                <image>
            <title>Latest Switch Game Metascores on Metacritic</title>
            <description>We Deal With Criticism</description>
            <url>https://www.metacritic.com/images/layout/mc_logo_big.png</url>
            <width>144</width>
            <height>73</height>
            <link>https://www.metacritic.com</link>
        </image>
        

    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ring Fit Adventure]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Traverse grass-swept plains by jogging in place, attack enemies with overhead shoulder presses, and refill your health meter by striking some yoga poses. Two new accessories, the Ring-Con™ and Leg Strap, measure your real-world actions and help turn them into in-game movements. With additional minigames and customizable workout routines, Ring Fit Adventure is great escape for players of all skill levels and schedules. In Adventure mode, defeat enemies with attacks based on real-world exercises as you traverse more than 100 levels in over 20 worlds. As you work through each level (and possibly work up a sweat), you’ll earn experience points. Between fights, you may encounter some unusual methods of transportation such as squat-powered launch pads. Then, pass around the Ring-Con and leg strap accessories and select from a few minigames: break boxes with gusts of air, craft pottery using squats, and more.<p>Publisher: Nintendo<p>Release Date: Oct 18, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/ring-fit-adventure ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Felix the Reaper]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Felix The Reaper is a romantic comedy about the life of Death. A 3D shadow manipulation puzzle adventure game of dance, dying people and love. Felix works at The Ministry of Death and is in love with Betty The Maiden from The Ministry of Life. He believes that going to the human world as a field reaper will enable him to one day meet her. Hence he’s taken the job of making sure people die – and taught himself to dance to impress the love of his life. Since Felix only moves in the shadows, he needs to manipulate his surroundings to find his way through the world. Luckily reapers like Felix are able to turn the sun and move shadowing objects around. This enables him to create the necessary shadow paths. He does so to solve the adventure plots, that makes people die according to the ministerial plans.<p>Publisher: Daedalic Entertainment<p>Release Date: Oct 17, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/felix-the-reaper ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stranded Sails: Explorers of the Cursed Islands]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Stranded Sails is an open world exploration farming adventure full of discoveries and quests! Along with your crew you are ship-wrecked on a mysterious archipelago. Now it's up to you to secure your survival and solve the mysteries deep in the heart of the islands – and finally escape.<p>Publisher: Merge Games<p>Release Date: Oct 17, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/stranded-sails-explorers-of-the-cursed-islands ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Little Town Hero]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                GAME FREAK, the developer of the Pokémon series, has created a new RPG for Nintendo Switch. In TOWN, players must take up arms against invading monsters, all within the walls of a single village.<p>Publisher: Nintendo<p>Release Date: Oct 16, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/little-town-hero ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Planescape: Torment: Enhanced Edition / Icewind Dale: Enhanced Edition]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Planescape: Torment Enhanced Edition

"What can change the nature of a man?" 

You are the Nameless One, a hulking figure covered in scars and tattoos collected over the course of countless livesnone of which you can remember, but are now coming back to haunt you. You are prodded awake by Morte, a floating skull and keeper of secrets, to embark on an adventure from the dirty streets of Sigil through the mysterious Outer Planes and even into the depths of Hell itself. 

Soon, you will discover that some destinies cannot be escaped and some memories are greater burdens than an even an immortal can bear. 

Contains: 

* Original Planescape: Torment campaign 
* Restored quest content, cut from the original game 

The Planes Await 
Explore the furthest and most bizarre reaches of the Dungeons & Dragons multiverse, filled with strange magics, talking weapons, philosophic undead, and more.

Strange Bedfellows 
A chaste succubus who can kill with a kiss. A confused crossbow-wielding cube. A suit of armor animated by a spirit demanding justice. Join these companions and more on your journey through the planes.

Optimized for Console
Experience Planescape: Torment in HD with a reworked interface designed for Console

Icewind Dale Enhanced Edition 

Evil stirs beneath the Spine of the World. 

Journey deep into Icewind Dale, a harsh and unforgiving territory settled only by the hardiest folk. Battle the cunning, ferocious beasts that survive among the snow-shrouded peaks, and confront an evil that schemes to wreak destruction upon the world. 

Originally released in 2000, Icewind Dale is a Dungeons & Dragons tactical isometric roleplaying game set in the legendary Forgotten Realms. 

Contains: 

* Original Icewind Dale campaign 
* Heart of Winter expansion 
* Trials of the Luremaster expansion 
* Adventurers of Neverwinter voice and portrait pack
* Restored quest content, cut from the original game 

New Character Options 
Select from over 30 new kits and classes to create the perfect adventuring party; customize your heroes with expanded options for hair, skin, and clothing colors, as well as new portraits and voice sets.

Gather Your Party 
Tackle the dangers of Icewind Dale alone or with friends in co-op multiplayer.

Optimized for Console
Experience Icewind Dale in HD with a reworked interface design!<p>Publisher: Skybound Games<p>Release Date: Oct 15, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/planescape-torment-enhanced-edition-icewind-dale-enhanced-edition ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt - Complete Edition]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                AKA "Switcher 3".... A whole world to explore, at home and on the go. The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt is a story-driven, open world adventure set in a dark fantasy universe. You are Geralt of Rivia, mercenary monster slayer. At your disposal is every tool of the trade: razor-sharp swords, lethal mixtures, stealthy crossbows, and powerful combat magic. Before you stands a war-torn, monster-infested continent you can explore at will. Your current contract? Tracking down the Child of Prophecy, a living weapon that can alter the shape of the world.

The Complete Edition contains every piece of downloadable content released for the game, including two massive story expansions: Hearts of Stone & Blood and Wine. It's the perfect opportunity to enter this world for the first time or relive the adventure on the go!

Features:

* A gigantic open world to explore.
 Visit the luxurious and corrupt city of Novigrad, face the frigid cold of the wind-swept Skellige islands, and challenge the dark forces roaming the forlorn, ravaged No Man's Land. Sail through open seas, dive in search of long lost artifacts or gallop your mount into combat the world of the Witcher beckons to be explored.

* Unparalleled novel-like story spanning over 150 hours of gameplay.
 With over 100 hours of core and side-quest gameplay and over 50 hours of additional content, The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt combines the intense, plot-driven pull of traditional RPGs with the freedom of choice only open world games can offer. Make choices and face their consequences to unlock endings tailored to how you play.

* Now on Switch play at home and on the go.
 Developed to take advantage of everything Nintendo Switch has to offer, the game delivers a truly powerful on-the-go experience.<p>Publisher: Warner Bros. Interactive Entertainment<p>Release Date: Oct 15, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/the-witcher-3-wild-hunt---complete-edition ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Ninja Saviors: Return of the Warriors]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                In TAITO’s latest arcade action title you’ll slip into the role of one of five android ninjas and brawl your way through waves of enemy hordes in a dystopian future. Over a total of eight levels, you’ll take on the tyrant Banglar and his henchmen either alone or - for the first time in the history of the series - with a friend. So settle into a night on the couch with your friends, and reminisce about the golden era of 90s co-op game evenings you know and love.<p>Publisher: Taito Corporation<p>Release Date: Oct 15, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/the-ninja-saviors-return-of-the-warriors ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Baldur's Gate and Baldur's Gate II: Enhanced Editions]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Includes the original Baldur’s Gate: Enhanced Edition and its sequel, Baldur’s Gate II: Enhanced Edition, with all DLC and restored quest content, as well as the Baldur’s Gate: Siege of Dragonspear expansion, featuring new original content developed by Beamdog to bridge the two games.<p>Publisher: Skybound Games<p>Release Date: Oct 15, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/baldurs-gate-and-baldurs-gate-ii-enhanced-editions ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Overwatch]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Welcome to Overwatch. Soldiers. Scientists. Adventurers. Oddities. In a time of global crisis, an international task force of heroes banded together to restore peace to a war-torn world: Overwatch. It ended the crisis and helped to maintain peace in the decades that followed, inspiring an era of exploration, innovation, and discovery. But after many years, Overwatch's influence waned, and it was eventually disbanded.

Overwatch is gone but the world still needs heroes.

Choose A Hero.

Overwatch features a wide array of unique heroes, ranging from a time-jumping adventurer, to an armored, rocket-hammer-wielding warrior, to a transcendent robot monk. Every hero plays differently, and mastering their abilities is the key to unlocking their potential. No two heroes are the same.

Play Your Role.

Offense
Defense
Tank
Support

Whether you're engaging in combat on the front line, providing defensive cover with your energy shield, or supporting your allies by amplifying their damage, every hero's abilities are designed to be effective as part of a team. Learning to utilize your abilities in concert with your teammates' is the key to victory.

Team-Based Objectives.

Teams of heroes do battle across the planet. From protecting the secrets of the mysterious Temple of Anubis, to safely escorting an EMP device through King's Row, the world is your battlefield.<p>Publisher: Blizzard Entertainment<p>Release Date: Oct 15, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/overwatch ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Killer Queen Black]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Fly solo, or team up with three of your friends as you race to complete one of three possible victory conditions. Killer Queen Black, a new take on the arcade eSport Killer Queen, has been rebuilt from the ground up and optimized for console. The gameplay is immediately recognizable and familiar, yet it introduces exciting new twists and online play for the home audience. Killer Queen Black is the follow up to Killer Queen that fans have been begging for. <p>Publisher: Liquid Bit<p>Release Date: Oct 11, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/killer-queen-black ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doraemon: Story of Seasons]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Doraemon, the endearing cat-type robot that captured the hearts of millions worldwide, arrives for another adventure in ‘Doraemon Story of Seasons’! Dive into a new world that combines relaxing gameplay with a story of farming, friendship and helping others. Grab a shovel and join the fun.<p>Publisher: Bandai Namco Games<p>Release Date: Oct 11, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/doraemon-story-of-seasons ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Valfaris]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Set in a far corner of space, Valfaris is a heavy metal infused 2D action-platformer and the next game from the team behind Unity Awards finalist, Slain: Back From Hell. Brutal combat. Deadly enemies. Stunning pixel art. Savage soundtrack. Get ready to rip the galaxy a new wormhole. <p>Publisher: Merge Games<p>Release Date: Oct 10, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/valfaris ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mable & The Wood]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Mable & The Wood is a Metroidvania where you can take the form of the bosses that you kill, changing how you're able to explore the interconnected world. It's also a Metroidvania where you don't have to kill anyone. The strange cult that resurrected you speak of an ancient prophecy that says you will hunt down the great beasts, take their shape, and use their powers to save this dying world. But what if they're wrong? The prophecy is old, and words lose their meaning with time... When the world is falling apart around you, what will you do? In Mable & The Wood, it's up to you to make that choice. You don't have to kill anyone, but you might kill everyone.<p>Publisher: Graffiti Games<p>Release Date: Oct 10, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/mable-the-wood ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Knight's Quest]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                A gorgeous action adventure on an epic scale. Play as Rusty, a clumsy adventurer who accidentally sets about the end of the world. Solve mind-bending puzzles, fight challenging enemies, defeat huge bosses and platform your way through a fantastic open world.<p>Publisher: Curve Digital<p>Release Date: Oct 10, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/a-knights-quest ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trine 4: The Nightmare Prince]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                The Trine series returns to the magic of 2.5D with Trine 4: The Nightmare Prince! The three heroes of the best-selling adventure series are back, sent on a quest to retrieve the troubled young Prince Selius. Amadeus the Wizard, Pontius the Knight, and Zoya the Thief are joined together once again on a thrilling quest through fantastical fairytale landscapes teeming with danger.   Prince Selius suffers from intensely dark dreams and, due to his magical talents, monstrous nightmares are able to slip into reality and wreak havoc on the waking world. Amadeus, Pontius, and Zoya must find the afflicted prince and resolve the desperate situation before the world is engulfed by the Nightmare Prince's shadows.<p>Publisher: Modus Games<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/trine-4-the-nightmare-prince ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Alliance Alive HD Remastered]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                An age of darkness has befallen the world. The Dark Current, a cataclysmic event caused by the Daemons’ emergence, has decimated the population and divided land into separate regions, leaving the survivors to be subjugated by Daemonic overlords.<p>Publisher: NIS America<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/the-alliance-alive-hd-remastered ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Call of Cthulhu: The Official Video Game]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Plunge into Cyanide Studio's Call of Cthulhu, the official Cthulhu videogame inspired by Chaosium's classic pen and paper RPG. Uncover the chilling mysteries of this RPG-investigation game, descending deep into a world of cosmic horrors, creeping madness, and shrouded Old Gods within Lovecraft's iconic universe.

The Cthulhu Mythos has been fascinating audiences for generations, growing to become one of the largest shared universes ever envisioned and giving birth to countless stories, novels, movies, tabletop and videogames since the original publication of H.P. Lovecraft's The Call of Cthulhu. Adaptions and references have formed a widespread legacy stretching back to the very beginning of the 20th century, latching on to the key fear of the human psyche: that of the unknown. Now, Call of Cthulhu will bring the mythos to life like never before, on PlayStation 4, Xbox One and PC.

In this world, nothing is as it seems. Sanity is an irregular bedfellow, all too often replaced by the whisperings in the dark. Strange creatures, weird science, and shadowy cults dominate the Cthulhu Mythos, intent on realizing their mad schemes to bring about the end of everything. Your mind will suffer -- balancing a razor-thin line between sanity and madness, your senses will be disrupted until you question the reality of everything around you. Trust no one. Creeping shadows hide lurking figures... and all the while, the Great Dreamer prepares for his awakening.<p>Publisher: Focus Home Interactive<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/call-of-cthulhu-the-official-video-game ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Asphalt 9: Legends]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Asphalt 9: Legends features an extensive roster of real hypercars from renowned manufacturers such as Ferrari, Porsche, Lamborghini and W Motors. Pick your dream ride and race across spectacular locations around the world. Leave your friends in the dust and become a legend in your own group or break your limits to achieve worldwide glory.<p>Publisher: Gameloft<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/asphalt-9-legends ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[BurgerTime Party!]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                A Feast for the senses - chock-full of carefully crafted stages with new hazards such as icy ladders, conveyor belts, and fiery floors, along with colorful characters inspired by old-school cartoons <p>Publisher: XSEED Games<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/burgertime-party! ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yooka-Laylee and the Impossible Lair]]></title>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                Yooka & Laylee are back in a brand-new platform hybrid adventure. They must run, jump and roll their way through a series of challenging 2D levels, face a puzzling Overworld and rally the Royal Bee-tallion to take down Capital B and his Impossible Lair. 
* The overworld isn't just a hub to hop from level to level, it provides a whole separate gaming experience. Explore and unlock more 2D levels by completing objectives and puzzles, rescue Royal Bees and find collectibles.
* Alternate Level States. Think you've got a level figured out? Try it in its alternate state! Flip switches in the overworld to create new landscapes.
* Bee-at the Impossible Lair. Players are free to tackle Capital B's Impossible Lair at any time; however, they may find it too much of a challenge without the help of the Royal Bee Guards.<p>Publisher: Team 17<p>Release Date: Oct 08, 2019
                            ]]>
        </description>
        <link><![CDATA[ https://www.metacritic.com/game/switch/yooka-laylee-and-the-impossible-lair ]]></link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <category>Games, Movies, Tv, Music</category>
            </item>


    </channel>
</rss>
